{"problemsArray": [
  {"answer": "5, 69, 86", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(25, 69)\n(11, 5)\n(1, 86)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5, 7, 39", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(5, 16)\n(7, 75)\n(39, 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "35, 37, 56", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(56, 15)\n(35, 100)\n(37, 21)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-308", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n-3(5)^3 + 2(5)^2 + 4(5) - 3", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d -3x^3 + 2x^2 + 4x - 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "18, 68, 71", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(68, 16)\n(18, 61)\n(71, 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "149", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n4(3)^3 + 3(3)^2 + 3(3) + 5", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d 4x^3 + 3x^2 + 3x + 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10, 12, 58", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(58, 11)\n(10, 94)\n(12, 20)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "45", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n3(3)^3 - 3(3)^2 - 3(3)", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d 3x^3 - 3x^2 - 3x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, 65, 93", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(2, 93)\n(60, 6)\n(49, 65)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "30, 86, 100", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(100, 29)\n(30, 74)\n(86, 12)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "17", "explanation": "Substitute 4 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n5(4) - 3", "prompt": "f(4) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(4) when:\nf(x) \u003d 5x - 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9", "explanation": "Substitute 1 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n4(1)^3 + 2(1)^2 + 3(1)", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(1) when:\nf(x) \u003d 4x^3 + 2x^2 + 3x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "31", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n(3)^3 + 4", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d x^3 + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "21, 56, 71", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(71, 24)\n(21, 71)\n(56, 10)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "165", "explanation": "Substitute 4 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n2(4)^3 + 3(4)^2 - 2(4) - 3", "prompt": "f(4) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(4) when:\nf(x) \u003d 2x^3 + 3x^2 - 2x - 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11, 17, 37", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(28, 37)\n(37, 17)\n(23, 11)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "213", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n2(5)^3 - 2(5)^2 + 2(5) + 3", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d 2x^3 - 2x^2 + 2x + 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, 9, 91", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(28, 91)\n(24, 4)\n(10, 9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "27, 78, 80", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(80, 5)\n(27, 90)\n(78, 8)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "19, 21, 31", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(29, 31)\n(88, 19)\n(4, 21)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "17", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n5(3) + 2", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d 5x + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Substitute 1 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n-2(1)^2 + 3(1) + 1", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(1) when:\nf(x) \u003d -2x^2 + 3x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, 4, 19", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(24, 3)\n(21, 19)\n(15, 4)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5, 21, 99", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(99, 31)\n(21, 72)\n(5, 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11", "explanation": "Substitute 1 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n5(1)^3 + 2(1) + 4", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(1) when:\nf(x) \u003d 5x^3 + 2x + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "16", "explanation": "Substitute 2 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n4(2)^2", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(2) when:\nf(x) \u003d 4x^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "22", "explanation": "Substitute 2 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n3(2)^3 - 2", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(2) when:\nf(x) \u003d 3x^3 - 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "13, 47, 78", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(13, 19)\n(47, 49)\n(78, 14)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Substitute 1 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n4(1)^3 + 3(1)^2 - 3", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(1) when:\nf(x) \u003d 4x^3 + 3x^2 - 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11, 45, 75", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(16, 75)\n(49, 11)\n(48, 45)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "125", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n3(3)^3 + 3(3)^2 + 5(3) + 2", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d 3x^3 + 3x^2 + 5x + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "445", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n3(5)^3 + 3(5)^2 - (5)", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d 3x^3 + 3x^2 - x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10, 22, 50", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(27, 22)\n(2, 10)\n(46, 50)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4", "explanation": "Substitute 1 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n4(1)", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(1) when:\nf(x) \u003d 4x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "101", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n3(5)^2 + 5(5) + 1", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d 3x^2 + 5x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "157", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n5(3)^3 + 3(3)^2 - 2(3) + 1", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d 5x^3 + 3x^2 - 2x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-4", "explanation": "Substitute 1 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n-3(1)^3 - (1)", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(1) when:\nf(x) \u003d -3x^3 - x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "15, 21, 69", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(27, 15)\n(2, 21)\n(18, 69)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2", "explanation": "Substitute 4 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n(4) - 2", "prompt": "f(4) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(4) when:\nf(x) \u003d x - 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "315", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n3(5)^3 - 3(5)^2 + 3(5)", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d 3x^3 - 3x^2 + 3x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "15, 16, 91", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(15, 16)\n(77, 15)\n(23, 91)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "30, 48, 78", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(7, 30)\n(12, 48)\n(13, 78)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "4, 39, 43", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(4, 18)\n(43, 6)\n(39, 11)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "32, 39, 45", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(5, 39)\n(50, 45)\n(4, 32)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-20", "explanation": "Substitute 2 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n-3(2)^3 - (2)^2 + 5(2) - 2", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(2) when:\nf(x) \u003d -3x^3 - x^2 + 5x - 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "27, 47, 58", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(58, 31)\n(47, 83)\n(27, 9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "5, 13", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(8, 5)\n(4, 13)\n(38, 13)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "108", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n5(3)^3 - 2(3)^2 - 3(3)", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d 5x^3 - 2x^2 - 3x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "0", "explanation": "Substitute 1 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n-2(1)^3 + 1 + 1", "prompt": "f(1) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(1) when:\nf(x) \u003d -2x^3 + x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "245", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n2(5)^3 - (5)", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d 2x^3 - x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-43", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n-(3)^3 - (3)^2 - 3(3) + 2", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d -x^3 - x^2 - 3x + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "16, 37, 77", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(77, 34)\n(37, 20)\n(16, 14)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "10, 18, 23", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(23, 6)\n(18, 35)\n(10, 13)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "369", "explanation": "Substitute 4 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n5(4)^3 + 3(4)^2 + 4 - 3", "prompt": "f(4) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(4) when:\nf(x) \u003d 5x^3 + 3x^2 + x - 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11, 48, 73", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(11, 23)\n(48, 73)\n(73, 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "23, 25, 51", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(51, 14)\n(25, 34)\n(23, 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-205", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n-2(5)^3 + 2(5)^2 - (5)", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d -2x^3 + 2x^2 - x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "620", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n5(5)^3 - (5)^2 + 4(5)", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d 5x^3 - x^2 + 4x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "19, 38, 53", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(30, 38)\n(32, 19)\n(17, 53)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "215", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n(5)^3 + 3(5)^2 + 3(5)", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d x^3 + 3x^2 + 3x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "22", "explanation": "Substitute 2 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n3(2)^2 + 5(2)", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(2) when:\nf(x) \u003d 3x^2 + 5x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "3, 20, 60", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(26, 60)\n(64, 3)\n(12, 20)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "35, 43, 66", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(66, 21)\n(35, 35)\n(43, 23)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "55", "explanation": "Substitute 2 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n5(2)^3 + (2)^2 + 4(2) + 3", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(2) when:\nf(x) \u003d 5x^3 + x^2 + 4x + 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "31, 67, 74", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(67, 5)\n(31, 59)\n(74, 19)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "9, 26, 46", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(26, 22)\n(46, 40)\n(9, 8)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "41", "explanation": "Substitute 4 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n3(4)^2 - 2(4) + 1", "prompt": "f(4) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(4) when:\nf(x) \u003d 3x^2 - 2x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "255", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n2(5)^3 - (5)^2 + 5(5) + 5", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d 2x^3 - x^2 + 5x + 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "89", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n2(3)^3 + 4(3)^2 - 1", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d 2x^3 + 4x^2 - 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11, 23, 53", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(11, 33)\n(23, 100)\n(53, 3)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "7, 60, 93", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(60, 9)\n(7, 17)\n(93, 7)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-28", "explanation": "Substitute 2 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n-3(2)^3 - 2(2)^2 + 2(2)", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(2) when:\nf(x) \u003d -3x^3 - 2x^2 + 2x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "427", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n3(5)^3 + 2(5)^2 + 2", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d 3x^3 + 2x^2 + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "6, 12, 22", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(3, 6)\n(60, 12)\n(34, 22)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "40, 58, 65", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(65, 26)\n(40, 75)\n(58, 6)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "12, 30, 81", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(12, 8)\n(30, 95)\n(81, 22)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "145", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n4(3)^3 + 3(3)^2 + 4(3) - 2", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d 4x^3 + 3x^2 + 4x - 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "31, 72, 90", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(72, 19)\n(31, 85)\n(90, 21)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "52", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n2(3)^3 - 2(3)^2 + 5(3) + 1", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d 2x^3 - 2x^2 + 5x + 1", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "630", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n4(5)^3 + 5(5)^2 + 5", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d 4x^3 + 5x^2 + 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "17, 40, 44", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(44, 17)\n(17, 62)\n(40, 12)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "8, 64, 100", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(64, 14)\n(8, 44)\n(100, 9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-66", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n-3(3)^3 + 2(3)^2 - 3", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d -3x^3 + 2x^2 - 3", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "142", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n5(3)^3 + 3 + 4", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d 5x^3 + x + 4", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "21, 63, 84", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(84, 19)\n(21, 23)\n(63, 11)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-28", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n-2(3)^3 + (3)^2 + 5(3) + 2", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d -2x^3 + x^2 + 5x + 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "11, 13, 14", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(12, 11)\n(21, 14)\n(22, 13)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "37, 89, 97", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(12, 97)\n(14, 37)\n(21, 89)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "20, 54, 72", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(54, 2)\n(20, 55)\n(72, 19)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "25, 44, 83", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(4, 44)\n(34, 25)\n(18, 83)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "270", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n(5)^3 + 5(5)^2 + 4(5)", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d x^3 + 5x^2 + 4x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "325", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n3(5)^3 - 3(5)^2 + 5(5)", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d 3x^3 - 3x^2 + 5x", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "20, 51, 52", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(22, 51)\n(25, 20)\n(17, 52)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "22", "explanation": "Substitute 2 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n5(2)^2 + 2(2) - 2", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(2) when:\nf(x) \u003d 5x^2 + 2x - 2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "325", "explanation": "Substitute 5 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n3(5)^3 - 2(5)^2", "prompt": "f(5) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(5) when:\nf(x) \u003d 3x^3 - 2x^2", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "2, 30, 73", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(31, 30)\n(11, 2)\n(16, 73)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "26, 37, 72", "explanation": "In this example, the domain consists of the x values", "question": "Find the domain of:\n(72, 27)\n(26, 3)\n(37, 9)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "19, 67, 74", "explanation": "In this example, the range consists of the y values", "question": "Find the range of:\n(28, 74)\n(78, 19)\n(4, 67)", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "-3", "explanation": "Substitute 2 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n-3(2)^2 + 2(2) + 5", "prompt": "f(2) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(2) when:\nf(x) \u003d -3x^2 + 2x + 5", "type": "text"},
  {"answer": "54", "explanation": "Substitute 3 for all x\u0027s in the function and simplify:\n5(3)^2 + 3(3)", "prompt": "f(3) \u003d", "question": "Find the value of f(3) when:\nf(x) \u003d 5x^2 + 3x", "type": "text"}
]}